chubbybrain.com 2010-06-14

# :: Welcome to ChubbyBrain :: Privacy Policy

| ChubbyBrain Privacy Policy  
---  
  
LAST MODIFIED: February 17, 2009

This privacy policy applies to your use of the website located at www.chubbybrain.com (ChubbyBrain) and, but not does apply to any third party sites that may be linked to them, or any relationships you may have with the business listed on ChubbyBrain.

The terms "we", "us" and “CPM” refer to CPM LLC. The terms "you" and "your" refer to you, as a user of any of ChubbyBrain. The term "personal information" means information that you provide to us which personally identifies you to be contacted or identified, such as your name, phone number, email address, and any other data that is tied to such information.  
BY USING CHUBBYBRAIN, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE CHUBBYBRAIN.

  1. **Information We Collect and How We Use It  
**We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the collection of personal information is limited to that which is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified below. If we use your information in a manner different than the purpose for which it is collected, then we will ask you for your consent prior to such use.

**Account information**. If you create an account to take advantage of the full range of services offered on ChubbyBrain, we ask for and record personal information such as your name and email address. We use your email address to send you updates and news, and contact you on behalf of other users (such as other users who send you private messages). You may choose not to receive e-mail of this type by accessing the “Alerts & Subscriptions” tab within the "Edit Profile" page on ChubbyBrain and updating your settings.

**Submissions.** We store and may publicly display your submissions in order to provide the services that we offer. When we display your submissions, we do so together with your account name (first name and last initial or first name and last name if you’ve opted in to reveal your last name). The term "submissions" refers to the information that you submit or post to ChubbyBrain for public display, such as company ratings, reviews, comments and the information that you display as part of your expert profile.

**Feedback**. If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication.

**Private messaging.** In order to allow you to send and receive personal messages to other registered users of ChubbyBrain, we record the messages that you send and receive using ChubbyBrain's private messaging feature.

**Activity**. We record information relating to your use of ChubbyBrain, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer ChubbyBrain and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of ChubbyBrain. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information.

**Cookies.** We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely indentify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term "cookies" refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of ChubbyBrain may not work properly or at all.

Enforcement. We may use the information we collect in connection with your use of ChubbyBrain (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

  2. **Transfer of Information  
**We may distribute your submissions to third parties, as permitted pursuant to our Terms of Service. The third parties may in turn publicly display or publish your submissions in connection with their own websites and media platforms. When we distribute your submissions to third parties, we typically include your account name (but not your personal information unless you include your personal information in your submissions).

We may share your personal information with third parties to provide you with services that we offer through ChubbyBrain, conduct quality assurance testing, facilitate creation of accounts, provide technical and customer support, or provide specific services, such as synchronization of your contacts with other software applications, in accordance with your instructions. These third parties are required not to use your personal information other than to provide the services requested by you.

We may share your personal information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, "Affiliates") that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company or our assets, that company will possess your personal information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy; (c) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that we receive.

We may disclose information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertising banners.  
We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit ChubbyBrain. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

  3. **Links  
**ChubbyBrain may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.
  4. **Controlling Your Personal Data  
**To the extent you include personal information in your submissions (such as a photo of yourself), third parties may be able to identify you, associate you with your user account and contact you. Third parties can also associate you with your user account, but only if the third party already knows your full name and you include information in your submission that allows the third party to distinguish you from other users who might share the same full name. Please do not include information in your submissions that you expect to keep private.

Please also note that the personal messages you send or receive using ChubbyBrain's private messaging feature are only private to the extent that you and the sender/recipient keep them private. For example, we do not have any control over whether a recipient of one of your personal messages publicly posts the contents of such a message.

As a registered ChubbyBrain user, you can modify some of your personal information and your privacy preferences by accessing the "Edit Profile" section of this website. For example, you may choose not to receive e-mail solicitations from ChubbyBrain by accessing the "Alerts & Subscriptions" tab within the “Edit Profile” section on ChubbyBrain and updating your notification settings. Upon your request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to close your account, and cease displaying your name in association with your submissions on ChubbyBrain; nevertheless, we may still retain your personal information in our systems.

  5. **Security  
**Your account is password protected. We use industry standard measures to protect the personal information that is stored in our database. We limit the access to your personal information to those employees and contractors who need access to perform their job function, such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security on ChubbyBrain, please contact us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

You hereby acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

  6. **E-mails and Opt-out  
**You may opt-out of receiving e-mail notifications under the "Alerts & Subscriptions” tab of the “Edit Profile” section after you log on to ChubbyBrain. Unregistered users who receive e-mails from us may also opt-out of receiving further e-mails by following the instructions contained in our e-mails. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you e-mail notifications of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.
  7. **Terms and Modifications to this Privacy Policy  
**We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will post any new versions on this page. If we make any material changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any such changes will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our website. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of ChubbyBrain. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your personal information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of ChubbyBrain following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
  8. **Dispute Resolution  
**If you believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may write to our Privacy Office at the following address:

Sachin@mehtalegal.com CPM LLC

11 Broadway  
Suite #1168  
New York, NY 10004

In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible ways in which you believe the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.

  9. **Contacting the Website and Access to Your Personal Information  
**Upon written request, subject to certain exceptions, we will inform you of the existence, use, and disclosure of your personal information and will give you access to that information. Access requests should be sent to our Privacy Officer, using the contact information above. When requesting access to your personal information, we may request specific information from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access, as well as to search for and provide the personal information that we hold about you. We may charge you a fee to access your personal information to cover our costs; however, we will advise you of any fee in advance, which will be no more than any maximum fee prescribed by law.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact us using the contact information listed above.
